

EDUCATION

BSC. COMPUTER SCIENCE

Anchor University

OND GEOLOGY

University of Lagos

BSC. ANATOMY

University of Benin

CERTIFICATION

COURSERA CERTIFICATES

- UI/UX Specialization
- Graphic Design & Design Principles
- Front-End Development

Phone

- +234 81 2017 9204
- +234 90 3852 0113

Email

ojeriakhijeza@gmail.com jezaojeriakhi@gmail.com

Address

Oklar Royale Ave, Lagos, Nigeria.

Zip Code - 100234

Portfolio

https://sites.google.com/view/jezaojeriakhi **Development:**

https://jezastudio.github.io/portfolio

JEZA OJERIAKHI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative Designer with over 8 years of experience working with growing businesses and individuals to achieve their goals. Confident in my ability to take on a both a designer and developer role, as well as collaborate with teams or individuals, to provide solutions to businesses needs.

IMPORTANT SKILLS:

- Front-End Dev.

- Graphic Design
- Illustrations
- Time Management

- Communication

- Branding
- Motion Graphics
- Social Media Management

- UI/UX Design
- Product Design - Problem Solving
- Teamwork & Collaboration

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Oaks Communication Ltd/ Lagos Nigeria (2017-2018)

- Developing unique brand identities, logos, and comprehensive brand guidelines.
- Developing innovative ad creatives for various digital channels.
- Incorporating feedback and revisions to refine designs and achieve client satisfaction.

VISUAL DESIGNER

Parachute Design Group/Toronto Canada (2018-2020)

- From creating graphic designs & motion graphics to creating brand identities and social media management.
- Designing and implementing creative UI/UX solutions.
- Creating compelling pitch decks.
- Managing multiple projects and meeting deadlines.

CREATIVE DESIGNER / ART DIRECTOR

Explicit Communication/Lagos Nigeria (2020-2023)

- Working with a team of talented creatives and a marketing team in creating designs, handling content creation and coming up with intuitive brand marketing strategies.
- Developing and maintaining responsive web interfaces using HTML, CSS and JavaScript

SOFTWARE SKILL

Adobe photoshop	Microsoft Office Tools	Adobe inDesign
Adobe Illustrator	CorelDraw	Adobe XD
Figma	HTML-S/CSS-3	
Adobe Animate	WordPress	